Guide to the Joseph Veverka papers, 1942-2013,
Veverka, Joseph papers,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Joseph Veverka papers, 1942-2013, bulk 1980-2000.
14-7-4318
Veverka, Joseph.
27.6 cubic feet.
Correspondence, publications, photographs, reports, printed material.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection contains course materials for Cornell classes in Astronomy, committee and group files relating to different organizations, workshops, and meetings as well as research and notes, mission files for Voyager, Galileo, Stardust-NExT, Near Earth Asteroid Rendezvous (NEAR), and CONTOUR among others. The collection also includes CRSR materials and grants and contracts for the various projects in which Veverka was involved.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Joseph Veverka was born in 1941 in Czechoslovakia (now the Czech Republic) and emigrated to Canada in 1951. Veverka received his B.S. in Physics from Queen's University and his Ph.D. from Harvard in 1970. At Cornell, Veverka was the James A. Weeks Professor of Physical Sciences, professor of Astronomy. His research area focused on physical studies of satellite surfaces and planetary rings. He was the principal investigator of the NASA Discovery Program mission CONTOUR, a co-investigator of the Deep Impact space mission to Comet Tempel 1, and is the principal investigator on the NASA Discovery Mission of Opportunity, Stardust-NExT. He is the recipient of the 2001 National Air and Space Museum Trophy. (via Wikipedia)
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection contains course materials for Cornell classes in Astronomy, committee and group files relating to different organizations, workshops, and meetings as well as research and notes, mission files for Voyager, Galileo, Stardust-NExT, Near Earth Asteroid Rendezvous (NEAR), and CONTOUR among others. The collection also includes CRSR materials and grants and contracts for the various projects in which Veverka was involved.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Veverka, Joseph.
Subjects:
Astronomy.; Celestial bodies.; Comets.; Galileo project.; NASA space programs.; Near Earth Asteroid Rendezvous Mission.; Stardust Mission.; Voyager project.
Places:
Outer space -- Exploration.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to Box 5 Folder 5, Box 9 Folder 53, Box 15 Folder 1, Box 25 Folders 2-3, 47-48, 50-53, Box 26 Folders 1-7, 10-11, 13-17, 41, Box 27 CDs/DVDs, Box 29 Folders 2-3, 45-46 restricted until 2038 or by permission of all associated mission partners.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Committee and Group Files
Series II. Articles by Others
Series III. Notes and Files
Series IV. Mission Files
Series V. Course Materials
Series VI. Correspondence
Series VII. Veverka Articles and Awards
Series VIII. Personal Records
Series IX. Grants and Contracts
Series X. Audio/Visual Material
Series XI. Conferences and Talks
Series XII. Departmental Files
Series XIII. Objects
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Committee and Group Files
  - American Geophysical Union (AGU) - Flinn Award Committee 7/94-7/96, 1994-07-1996-01 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - AGU - Matson, 1994-07-1994-12 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Amateur radio satellite organization (AMSAT), 1992-01-1993-01 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Includes letters in German
  - Dec. 10, 2006 Applied Physics Laboratory (APL) Colloquium, 2006-11-2006-12 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - The Next Steps for Human Space Exploration: What are the Alternatives?, 2006-12-1; DVD-2815 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Giovanelli Symposium, 2006-09-2006-10 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Arecibo Oct. 26-29/99 JV, 1999-10 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Astronomy Department Highlights, Undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Joe - State of Astronomy Dept., 1999-06-2002-06 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Association of Universities for Research in Astronomy (AURA), 1986-10-1987-06 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Nov. 9-12, 2006 Belton Symposium, 1994-2006-11 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    Includes related paper published in Icarus
  - Belton Symposium Journey Through the Solar System, 2006-11-10-2006-11-11; DVD-2816 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Belton Symposium, 2006; DVD-2817 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Burns Symposium, 2006-02-2006-07 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Burns Symposium, 2006-07 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Mark Campbell Tenure Case, 2004-01-2004-02 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Michael Casper, 2001-10-2002-02 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Cerro Chajnantor Atacama Telescope (CCAT) - Pres. Skorton, 2006-03-2006-10 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    Includes letter about advising students, includes photographs
  - CCAT, 2006-06-2010-03 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - CCAT, 2005-07-2006-09 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Camera Hand-lens And Microscope Probe (CHAMP), 2004-04-2004-07 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Cornell NAIC Oversight Committee (CNOC), Feb, 3, 2003, 2002-12-2003-02 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - CNOC, Oct. 2, 2002, 2002-09-2004-06 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Includes a manila folder marked confidential
    RESTRICTED
  - CNOC May 16, 2002, 2002-05 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Space Research (COSPAR) (Stardust-NExT) Montreal, 7/13/08, 2008-07 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Space Operations Center (CSOC) 1-22-01, 2001-01 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Dec. 10, 2006 Applied Physics Laboratory (APL) Colloquium, 2007-03-2007-09 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Discovery At 15 Looking Back, Moving Forward, DVD-2819 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Discovery At 15: Looking Back, Looking Forward, DVD-2820 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - American Astronomical Society Division for Planetary Sciences (DPS) LAX Oct. 8-11, 2006 Joe, 2006-07-2006-10 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Includes 2 scientific publications/journals
  - DPS 10/06, DVD-2818 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - DPS, 1986-06-1993-06 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Eikenberry Proposal 7/99, 1999-07-19-1999-07-20 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Charles Elachi, 2006-08-27-2006-09-21 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Elachi Cornell, CD-4788 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - ESA/NASA Primitive Body Mission, 1983-10-1985-09 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Clementine Review 4/27/95 - jv, 1995-03-1995-04 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Exobiology Workshop, 1984-09-1985-09 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Exobiology Workshop, 1983-01-1984-09 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Special Symposium for Friends of Astronomy June 4-5, 2004, 2004-02-2004-06 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Friends/Ast. June 2003, 2003-06 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Friends of Astronomy, 2000-10-2006-10 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Thurs, Oct 4, 01, Fred Yooung, 2001-10 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    Includes October 2000 Cornell Chronicle
  - 14-16 Sept 2000, Friends mtg., 2000-06-2000-10 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Cowie photo, Sept. 2000, 2000-09-2001-01 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Friends Letter 2001-2002 Aug 1/2002, 2001-08 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Caltech 1/17-1/20/05, 2004-10-2005-01 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Tommy Gold Memorial Oct 13/04, 1998-01-2004-10 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Tommy Gold Memorial, 2004-07-2004-10 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Harpur Forum, 1997-07-1997-09 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Chambliss Award - Martin Hewitt, 2006-09-2006-10 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Ed Hewitt 11/7/03, 2003-06-2003-10 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Mr. Ed. Hewitt, 2000-04-2004-03 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Hewitt, 2000-03-2005-04 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Hewitt - Undergrad. Facility, 1999-02-2000-07 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Honeybee, 2006-05-2006-07 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Radio Antenna Proposal 1/15/04 Josephine Hopkins Foundation, 2004-01-2004-06 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Institute of Astronomy and Astrophysics (IAA) Conference - Low-Cost Missions Pasadena Sept 12-14, 2007, 2007-11-2007-12 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - IAA Meeting July 6,2006 (B. Farquhar), 2005-11-2007-02 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - IAA Meeting, 2003-2006 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    Includes two relevant journal articles
  - IAA Meeting, 2006-03-2006-05 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Bob Farquhar Group Event July 5-6 2006, 2006-03-2006-06 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - International Halley Watch (IHW) (1987), 1986-10-1989-01 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - International Lunar Network, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Io, 1987-1999 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Muses-C Wrkshp - Hawaii - Mar 7-9,97, 1997-02-1997-03 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Muses-C, 1997-02-1999-06 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Muses-C Science Working Group (SWG) - 12/5/97 JV, 1997-10-1997-12 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Imaging Systems Science Team (ISST) June 86, 1986-04-1986-06 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    Includes a Photograph
  - ISST, 1986-02-1987-07 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - ISST Oct 16-85, 1985-08-1985-11 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - ISST Oct 16-85, 1985-10 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - ISST March 85 Meeting, 1984-12-1985-04 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - ISST - Jan 9, 1984-03-1985-01 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - ISST, 1985-02-1985-03 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Includes viewgraphs, some possibly dated earlier than 1985
  - ISST - June 13/14/85, 1985-03-1985-08 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - ISST, 1982-09-1985-03 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Includes two JPL publications
  - ISST, 1984-05-1985-01 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Imaging Systems Science Team Kona, Hawaii Oct 13/84, 1984-07-1984-10 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - ISST 9/84, 1984-03-1984-11 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - ISST 9/84, 1984-02-1984-09 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Institute of Space and Aeronautical Science (ISAS) - Japan - 12/4/96-12/7/96, 1996-04-1996-12 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - International Space Year (ISY) 2nd Pacific Conference - 10/13-15/92, 1992-01-1992-10 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Lunar and Asteroid Data Analysis Program (LADAP), 1995-08 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - LADAP Mtg. - 8/30-31 DC, 1995-08-1995-09 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - George Jacoby (WIYN) visit to CU, 2003-01 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Jet Propulsion Laboratory (JPL) Comet Camera, Undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Mars Observer, 1985-05 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Mars Observer, 1985-05 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Mars Observer, 1985-05 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - JPL Consulting Agreement Visiting Committee on Science 3/04, 2004-01-2004-03 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - JPL Consulting Agreement Visiting Committee on Science 3/04, 2004-03 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - JPL Space Camp 8/03, 2003-06-2003-07 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Dean Peter Le Page Visit 9/29/03, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Dean Peter Le Page Visit 9/29/03, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Laboratory for Atmospheric and Space Physics (LASP) Report Oct 25-27, 2010, 2010-10-2010-11 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Mariner 9 and 10, Undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Multimission Image Processing Laboratory (MIPL), 1983-01-1984-07 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - "The Spaceguard Survey" [Near Earth Object (NEO) Detection Wksp] D. Morrison, 1/25/92, 1992-01-1992-04 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Management and Operations Working Group (MOWG), 1994-07-1994-08 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - MUSES-C, 1996-08-1996-10 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - MUSES-C, 1996-09 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - MUSES-C, 1996-09-1996-10 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - 4 Dec 02 Bob Brown, 2002-11-2002-12 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - National Astronomy and Ionosphere Center (NAIC), 2002-01-2002-02 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - NAIC mtg 3-28-02 Arecibo, 2001-08-2002-03 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Atacama Meeting, 2002-05 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - NAIC mtg 15-17 Nov 2000, 2000-03-2000-11 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - National Air and Space Museum (NASM) - DC - 3/7/94, 1993-1996-01 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - NASM 1988, 1984-10-1988-09 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Includes paper published in Geophysical Research Letters
  - Morrison, 1992-10-1993-01 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - NEO Review Panel - DC - Aug. 30-Sept. 2 '92, 1992-01-1993 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - New Millenium SWG, 1993-10-1996-04 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - New Millenium SWG, 1994-09-1995-10 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - New Millenium SWG, 1994-09 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Orbital Sciences Corp. Nov 2007, 2007-11 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Orbiting Planetary Telescope (OPT), 1990-09 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - OPT, 1990-08-1990-09 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Palomar, 1999-05-1999-11 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Pegasus, 1990-04-1991-10 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Planetary Astronomy @ Cornell Overview Spring 2010, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Planetary Astronomy Panel 5/89, 1989-05-1990-03 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Providence - Planetary Panel, Astronomy and Astrophysics Survey Committee (AASC) JV 10/30, 1989-08-1989-10 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Planetary Geology Working Group, 1982-01-1982-03 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    Includes astronomical photographic prints
  - Planetary Geology Working Group, 1976-1981-08 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Planetary Geology Working Group, 1980-08-1981-12 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Planetary Geology Working Group, 1977-03-1980-10 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Planetary Geology Working Group agenda: minutes of last meeting, 1980-09 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Planetary Lunch Presentation Deep Impact 6/2/05, 2005-05 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Deep Impact Planetary Lunch, 2005-05-02; DVD-2831 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Safety Issues 1995, 1995-02-1998-06 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Sagan Lab, 1993-10-1994-11 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Small Bodies Assessment Group (SBAG) - Denver 1/13/09, 2009-01-2009-02 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Space Infrared Telescope Facility (SIRTF) Job, April 2002, 2002-03 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - SIRTF, 1986-06-1989-01 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Space Telescope Advisory Committee (STAC) Sept 90, 1990-07-1990-10 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Hubble Space Telescope (HST) Reviews - 2/91, 1991-02 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - HST Review Panel, 1989-01-1991-05 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - HST Review Panel, 1989-01-1989-03 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Space Telescope Review Panel JV 4/19-21, 4/24-25, 4/27-29, 1989-01-1989-04 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Space Telescope Science Institute (STSI) - Space Telescope Advisory Committee 9/24-25/90 JV, 1990-07-1990-10 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Space Telescope, 1987-05-1990-10 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Space Telescope, 1988-03-1988-08 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Space Telescope, 1987-04-1989-07 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Solar System Exploration Subcommittee (SSES) Mtg. 6/18-19/98, 1998-05-1998-07 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Discovery Subgroup Report 1-94, 1994-01 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - SSES, 1997-03-1997-04 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - SSES, 1996-07-1997-04 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - SSES, 1990-01-1991-03 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Small Missions to Asteroids and Comets (SMACS), 1993-12-1994-03 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Solar System Exploration Management Council (SSEMC), 1988-02-1989-06 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - SSEMC Meeting June 1988 Washington D.C., 1988-04-1988-08 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Blue Team Meeting - Sept 19, '90 JV, 1990-08-1990-09 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - SSEMC, 1987-10-1989-03 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - SSEMC Feb 26 1988 Washington Meeting, 1987-12-1988-02 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - SSES, 1992-09-1995-03 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - SSES Meeting - San Diego - 2/24-28-91 JV, 1991-02-1994-01 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - SSES, 1990-04-1998-06 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - M. Stasavage Space Sciences, 1930-1985 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Contains old scientific papers in French and German and an English translation by Prof. Veverka from 1967 of a Russian publication
  - University of Maryland, 2008-12 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Unversity of Maryland Review February 12-13 2009, 2001-05-2009-03 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Planning Committee for Workshop on US Civil Space Policy, 2007-08 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Universities Space Research Association (USRA), 1990-02-1990-03 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - USRA, 1990-03 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Voyager: Neptune Results, 1989-08-1989-09 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    Contains photos of Neptune
  - Voyager, 1989-07-1989-08 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Voyager, 1989-08 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Voyager May 3-5 JPL JV, 1989-01-1989-04 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Voyager: Feb 13/89 Team Meeting: JPL, 1989-02 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Voy. Neptune Jan/Feb 89, 1987-09-1989-07 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - 12/04/04 Boston - Whipple Memorial Joe, 2004-08-2004-12 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Fred Whipple 12/4/04 Memorial Presentation, Undated; CD-4939 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Whipple photo, Undated; CD-4940 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Fred Whipple Presentation 12/04, ZD-90 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Fred Whipple Memorial Service, 2004-12 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    Viewgraphs from the presentation
  - 7/16-20 Falmouth, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - 2GB flash drive, unlabeled, Undated; HD-41 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Earth and Space Sciences Division Visiting Committee External Review, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - NSF - NAIC review, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - NSF management Review of NAIC, 2002-12; CD-5133 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Series II. Articles by Others
  - Allen, C., 2001-07 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Bernat, D., 2010-12 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Berthoud, M.G., 2002-11 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Cruikshank, D., 2001-06 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Dermott, S., 2001-09 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Hanner, M., 2002-04 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Hayabusa, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Janesick, J., 1991 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Lamy, P., 2003 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Learner, Z., 2003-02-26 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - McCoy, T., 2001-08 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - McCunn, H. J., 2000 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Millis, R. L., 2001-08 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Noe Dobrea, E., 2001 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Ryan, O., 1999-07 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Sekanina, Z., 2000-09-2002-12 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Simonelli, D., 1993-2003-05 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Stern, A., 2001-08 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Weissman, P., 1996 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Yelle, R., 2001-08 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Extinction and Excitation of the Moleculr Hydrogen Emission in Orion, Undated (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - CRSR Articles, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Donn, Bertram, Undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Peter Silverglate and Yervant Terzian, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - J. M. Cordes et al., 1981 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - J. L. Elliot et al., 1977 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Joseph Burns and Mark Showalter, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Weissman, P., 1986 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Rephaeli, Y., 1980 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Roellig, T. L., 1981 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Stuart Shapiro and Ira Wasserman, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - H. A. Scott and R. V. E. Lovelace, Undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - F. Palla et al., 1982 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Salpeter, E. E., 1982 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - R. Saenz and S. Shapiro, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Salpeter, E. E., 1980 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - S. Shapiro and I. Wasserman, Undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - I. Wasserman and S. Shapiro, Undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - B. Balick et al., 1992 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - R. Duncan et al., Undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Golitsyn, G. S., 1977 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Squyres, S., 1984 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - S. Beckwith et al., 1982 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Helfenstein, P., 1986 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Wasserman, I., 1980 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - B. Zuckerman et al., 1979 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - H. E. Payne et al., 1981 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - D. Stinebring, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Goguen, J., 1981 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - P. Silvergate and Y. Terzian, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Burgasser, A., 2009 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Neufeld, M., 2012 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - EOS Newsletter Volume 92 Number 17, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Belton, M., 2010 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Modeling of Comets, Newborn, R. L., 2001-12-14 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Preface to Discovering the Cosmos, Undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Ehrenfreund, Pascale, 2000-2003 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Science Articles, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Serries III. Notes and Files
  - 1986 Uranus, 1983-1986 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Notes 1971, 1971-1977 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Mars Notes, 1973-1978 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Europa, 1983-03-1983-05 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Europa #2, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Sulfur Deposits Hawaii, 1984-10 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Notes 1972, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Goniometer IR, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Goniometer and Related Experimental Information, 1976-09-1976-12 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Goniometer Log Book I, 1973-04-1974-12 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Goniometer Log Book II, 1975-01-1976-06 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Goniometer Log Book III, 1976-06-1978-09 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Goniometer Log Book IV, 1978-09-1979-06 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Goniometer Log Book V, 1979-06-1980-12 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Goniometer Log Book VI, 1981-01-1982-04 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Gerry Stasavage Goniometer Wiring, 1970-1980 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Sulfur in Glass, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Notes 1979, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Notes, 1987-1989 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Notes 1976, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Mars Streaks 1992, 1990-1992 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Programs, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Practice Output / Notes, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Scientific American Article 1863, 1863 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Clayton-Clyde Lee article, photographs, Undated (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Notes planning astronomy lectures, Undated (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Letter sent to Cornell Astronomy Dept., 2013 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Calculations and notes for astronomy classes, Undated (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Joseph Veverka Notes Pocket Notebook, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Notes On Comets, Undated (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Phobos and Deimos Photometry Notes, Undated (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Astronomy Notes, 1977-1983 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Neutron Stars and Ocean Vents Notes, Undated (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Research Notes, 1898-1903 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    Includes copies of Harvard College Observatory Telegrams and Bulletins
  - Veverka Notes, 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Veverka Notes, 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 39)
- Series IV. Mission Files
  - Discovery Update - JV, 1991-05-20 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Eolian Phenomena on Mars, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - NASA Workshops, 1997-1999 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Photos, Undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
    Contains slides and photographs
  - Prints and Negatives for Publication, Undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - NASA Stickers, Undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Callisto/Ganymede Global Scale Planning Guides, Undated (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Satellite - Review Papers, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - MIPL - Integration and Test Plan, 1983-1986 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Enceladus and Saturn, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Astronomy Dept. Computer Proposal, National Science Foundation (NSF), 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF) Computer Proposal 2/89, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Computer Proposal 7/14/89, 1989-07-14 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Current Computer needs of the Department of Astronomy CRSR, Undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Center for Radiophysics and Space Research (CRSR)--Director--Cornell Correspondence, 1982-1989 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Patent Policy, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Jobs - Ads for, CRSR Cornell, 1980-1988 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Soviet-American Flight Dynamics Implementation Team Meeting, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Amalthea, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Discovery Proposals, Hummingbird, 1998-06-1998-10 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Government Affairs, 1999-10-2001-04 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Network, 2001-08 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Unlabeled CD, Undated; CD-5016 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Palomar, 2002-07 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - RASC Handbook (Gupta), 2000 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Stern Telecon, 2007-07 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Planetary Science Subcommittee June Washington DC, 2007-06 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Update on New Opportunities in Solar System Exploration, 2007-06-07-2007-06-08; CD-5021 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - NASA Exploration, 2006-03-2006-12 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    Includes both general exploration and Mars exploration
  - "Mars as Art" Screen Saver, Undated; CD-5025 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Tyco, 2006-03 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Vesper, 2007-05 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - APL Nereus, 2005-04-2005-06 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - 4660 Nereus Information, 2000-2005 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - New Frontiers Proposals, 2004-02 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    One is Comet Clippers, other two are Comet Surface Sample Return
  - Discovery, Mars Sample Return, 2008-2010 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    RESTRICTED until 2038 or by permission of all associated mission partners
  - Amor Discovery - AO NNH10ZDA007O, CD-5029 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    ITAR Controlled
  - Chiron, 1992-2010-03 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - EPOXI Denver, 2009-11 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Small Bodies Working Group and Sample Return, 1993-1995 (Box 25, Folder 6)